BERKAY ÖZGEN



Personal

Address 28 Haziran Mah Eski Istanbul Cad, Kent Konut 3 E11 D36 41060 Kocaeli

Phone number 05308316309

Email berkayozgen3337@gmail.com

Date of birth 14-10-1998

Place of birth Amasya

Gender Male

Marital status Single

Driving licence

Website www.github.com/berkay3337

LinkedIn www.linkedin.com/in/berkay-özgen

Interests

Biking Long Distances

Playing Guitar

Music

Simulation Games

Languages

Enalish Fransızca



Hi! I'm Berkay. I am a Computer Engineering Student at Kocaeli University. Until now, I worked on topics such as web development, android development, machine learning, artificial neural network. I learned C and Java programming languages at the university and had the opportunity to develop many projects in these languages. I also developed different kinds of mobile applications with the react native framework. I made front-end and back-end developments. I gained experience in languages and technologies such as C#, Asp.Net, Vue.js, Bootstrap, Html, CSS. I also developed my website using the Python language and Django framework. I am a determined person who loves to learn new information all the time. And I am someone who never gives up.

Education and Qualifications

Kuleli Military High School Sep 2012 - Jun 2016 Kuleli Military High School, İstanbul

Kocaeli University/Computer Engineering Sep 2018 - Jun 2022 Kocaeli University, Kocaeli

Anadolu University Open Education/Justice

Sep 2020 - Jun 2022 Anadolu University Open Education, Eskişehir

Work experience

Software Intern(Full Stack Developer)

Mar 2021 - Jul 2021

Jul 2021 - Aug 2021

VTC Enerji A.Ş., Kocaeli/İzmit

I worked on web development. I made front-end and back-end developments. I used technologies such as C#, Html5, Css, Bootstrap, Vue. is, Node, is

Project Intern

Enerjisa Başkent Elektrik Dağıtım A.Ş., Ankara/Çankaya

Skills

С	•	•	•	
C#				
Java			•	
HTML5				
Bootstrap				
Python				
Django				
Vue.js				
Node.js				
React Native				
SqI				
Css				
Asp.Net				
Docker				
Node.js				
Git				

Courses

Ethical Hacking Course Boğaziçi University CyberSecurity Center Jul 2020 - Jul 2020

Speed Reading Course Adil Mavis

Sep 2015 - Sep 2015

Achievements

I won the third prize in the TUBITAK inter-high school projects competition with the wireless pacemaker charging project.